lcrhealth.com 2019-04-19

# Privacy Policy - LCR Health

Section 1 – What Information Do We Collect?

Information Provided by You: We may collect personal information that you provide to us, such as your name, home address, e-mail address, telephone number, demographic information, and/or payment information, if used to make a purchase from our Website. The type of information that we may collect depends on your use of our Websites and what information you provide to us.

Cookies and Other Technology: Like many sites, our Website employs cookies, JavaScript tags and Web beacons (also known as clear GIF technology or "action tags") to speed your navigation of our Website, recognize you and your access privileges, and track usage of our Website. Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored as text files by your Internet browser on your computer's hard drive. We use both persistent cookies and third-party cookies. Persistent and third-party cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our customers to enhance your experience on our Website. Persistent cookies are used to make it easier for you to navigate our Website, and remain on your hard drive for an extended period of time. Third party cookies are only used for short-term tracking.

Most Internet browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can remove cookies by following the directions provided in your Internet browser's "Help" file. If you reject cookies, you may still use our Website, but your ability to use some areas of our Website, such as a shopping cart, may be limited and may not function properly. For third-party cookies, you may opt-out of these by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.

Analytical Information: We and our third-party service providers may also use a variety of technologies that automatically or passively collect information about how this Website is accessed and used (known as "Usage Information"). “Usage Information” may include the type of browser and device you used to access our Website, your operating system and application version, the web pages accessed by you, the time you accessed these web pages, preceding web page views, and your use of any features or applications on this Website. Statistical data like this helps us understand what is interesting and relevant to our customers, so we can best adapt our content for our customers’ benefit.

We and our third-party service providers may also automatically collect an IP address or other unique identifier information from the computer, mobile device, technology or other device you use to access this Website. We may use this information to, amongst other things, administer this Website, help diagnose server problems, analyze trends, track web page movements, help identify you and your shopping cart, and gather broad demographic information for collected use.

Third Party Information: We also may receive information about you from third parties that include our products or promotional offers if you opt-in to receive information from us. You may also choose to participate in a third party app or social media site through which you allow us to collect information about you, including personal information.

Section 2 – What Do We Do With Your Information?

We use the information that we collect about you for a variety reasons, including the following:

  * Verifying your identity;
  * Fulfilling your product orders;
  * Responding to your questions;
  * Providing you with access to certain areas and features of this Website;
  * Communicating with you about your purchases and activities on this Website;
  * Offers regarding products and services we may provide to you directly or through third-party partners (unless you opt-out of such communications);
  * Improving the Website and our customers’ experience; and
  * Sending notices or information.

We may share your Personal Information with parent entities, subsidiaries and affiliates of LCR Health™ for internal reasons, primarily for business and operational purposes. Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, we will not share any of your personal information with third parties without your specific consent. We may share non-personal information, such as user statistics or demographics, as specifically set forth in this Privacy Policy.

We also contract with certain vendors to assist us in providing services to our customers. These vendors use the personal information that you submit to us in order to perform the following tasks:

  * Order processing at checkout;
  * Credit card authorization and identity verification;
  * Order shipping and handling;
  * Emailing newsletters and other promotional materials;
  * Storing and “backing up” our customer records; and
  * Improving our Websites and our customers’ experience.

Finally, notwithstanding the foregoing, we may transfer and disclose information to third parties to comply with a legal obligation; at the request of governmental authorities; or otherwise to protect the rights, property, safety, or security of third parties, users of this Website, or the public.

Section 3 - Consent

This Website is governed by and operated in accordance with the laws of the State of California and the United States, and is intended for the enjoyment of residents of the United States. If you are located outside of the United States, please be aware that information we collect will be transferred to and processed in the United States.

By using this Website, or providing us with any information, you (a) acknowledge that this Website is subject to the laws of the State of California and the United States, (b) consent to the collection, processing, maintenance and transfer of such information in and to the United States and other applicable territories, in which the privacy laws may not be as comprehensive or equivalent to those in the country where you reside and/or are a citizen, and (c) waive any claims that may arise under those laws.

Section 4 - How do I withdraw my consent?

If, after you opt-in to our mailing list, you change your mind, then you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you at any time by contacting us at SUPPORT@LCRHEALTH.COM or mailing us at:

LCR Health  
22704 Ventura Blvd #485  
Woodland Hills, CA 91364, United States

Service 5 - Security

To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.

If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with a AES-256 encryption. Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards.

Service 6 - Children’s Privacy

We do not specifically market to children under the age of thirteen (13). Children may not use our services, and we do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of thirteen (13). We have no way of distinguishing the age of individuals who address our website. If a child has provided us with personal information, the parent or guardian should contact us to remove the information and opt out of promotional opportunities.

Service 7 - California Residents

Many browsers have a "Do Not Track" feature that allows you to instruct websites that you do not want them to track your online activities. These browser features are not uniform, so we are not currently set up to respond to this feature.

California residents who have provided their personal information to us may request data regarding disclosures of their information to third parties for direct marketing purposes. Such requests may be submitted to us by email at [SUPPORT@LCRHEALTH.COM](mailto:support@lcrhealth.com) or by mail at:

LCR Health  
Re: Privacy Compliance Officer  
22704 Ventura Blvd #485  
Woodland Hills, CA 91364

Please specify in your communication that you are making a "California Shine the Light" inquiry. We will respond to your inquiry within 30 days.

Service 8 - Changes To This Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.

If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.

Questions & Contact Information

If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at [SUPPORT@LCRHEALTH.COM](mailto:support@lcrhealth.com) or by mail at:

LCR Health  
Re: Privacy Compliance Officer  
22704 Ventura Blvd #485  
Woodland Hills, CA 91364

Effective date: 4/13/17
